const e="apes_ch10",t="Chapter 10",o=[{number:1,question:"Tree plantations",choices:["are an effective way to produce wood for paper mills.","have a high biological diversity.","are sustainable because the trees lock all necessary soil nutrients in place.","are composed of many different tree species."],correct:0},{number:2,question:"The most diverse and sustainable forest type is the",choices:["second-growth forest.","commercial forest.","old-growth forest.","tree plantation."],correct:2},{number:3,question:"Forests are important to the world's people because",choices:["all of the choices","they help to remove and store atmospheric carbon dioxide.","they are an important source of traditional medicines.","they help to maintain relatively stable world temperatures."],correct:0},{number:4,question:"We are cutting forests faster than they are able to replenish themselves.",choices:["True","False"],correct:0},{number:5,question:"The method of tree harvesting that is most damaging to the environment is",choices:["selective cutting.","strip cutting.","clear-cutting.","all of the choices"],correct:2},{number:6,question:"Forest fires are always a bad thing.",choices:["False","True"],correct:0},{number:7,question:"Which of the following is a consequence of unsustainable logging practices and deforestation?",choices:["increased soil erosion","loss of biodiversity","habitat loss and/or habitat fragmentation","all of the choices"],correct:3},{number:8,question:"Scientists think that at least one-half of the world's known species live in",choices:["tropical dryland forests.","the cooler, drier forests (temperate deciduous forests) of North America, Europe, and Asia.","the cold, dry forest (boreal forests) of Canada and Russia.","tropical rain forests."],correct:3},{number:9,question:"The Amazon basin is found in which country?",choices:["India","Costa Rica","Australia","Brazil"],correct:3},{number:10,question:"Fire as a tool of forest management",choices:["has been banned because the resulting destruction is greater than the benefits.","is very controversial among forest scientists since there is no agreement that fires are beneficial.","has been banned because of the danger of uncontrolled wildfires.","is important in removing organic debris so that larger forest fires may be prevented."],correct:3},{number:11,question:"Much of the wood cut in the U.S. is used to produce pulp for making paper. We could reduce the cutting of trees used for this purpose by",choices:["using less paper and using paper more efficiently.","all of the choices","making pulp from fast-growing plants instead of trees.","recycling more paper goods."],correct:1},{number:12,question:"Realistic ways that we can reduce tropical rainforest deforestation and promote sustainability include",choices:["preventing all cutting of tropical trees.","all of the choices","educating consumers about unsustainable practices and encouraging consumption of sustainable goods.","keeping people from using tropical forests."],correct:2},{number:13,question:"In rangelands and grasslands, livestock tend to gather around ________, making these areas particularly vulnerable to damage.",choices:["hilltops","fence rows","water","protected ravines"],correct:2},{number:14,question:"In developing nations, national parks are highly protected areas that act as sanctuaries to wildlife.",choices:["False","True"],correct:0},{number:15,question:"This environmental activist group, composed of more than 1 million members worldwide, is responsible for buying and protecting land, waterways, and wetlands.",choices:["The Nature Conservancy","PETA","The Environmental Protection Agency","Greenpeace"],correct:0},{number:16,question:"Biodiversity hot spots are",choices:["regions that have many rare and endangered plant and animal species.","geographical regions whose boundaries are contested between neighboring countries.","layers of sedimentary rock that are especially rich in fossils.","regions around nuclear testing zones that have higher than normal mutation rates due to increased radiation levels."],correct:0},{number:17,question:"Ecosystems that we have degraded are irreversibly damaged.",choices:["True","False"],correct:1},{number:18,question:".The process of fixing human-caused damage to natural ecosystems is called",choices:["ecological restoration.","creating artificial ecosystems.","ecosystem enhancement.","ecological replacement."],correct:0},{number:20,question:"Which best illustrates an intentional desire on the part of humans to share their habitats with other species?",choices:["leaving crumbs on countertops and floors that cockroaches have access to","planting bulbs, flowers, and shrubs that deer coincidentally like to eat","constructing beehives and planting flowers that attract honeybees","putting garbage in traditional waste cans that raccoons and possums have access to"],correct:2}],s={id:e,displayName:t,questions:o};export{s as default,t as displayName,e as id,o as questions};
